Mike North: 让我们先重命名这个文件。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Let's start
by renaming this file.
迈克 · 诺斯: 我要把它重新命名为 ts，我要去我的
&gt;&gt; Mike North: I'm renaming it to ts,
I'm going to go to my
添加允许隐式的，对不起,
tsconfig, and add allow implicit, sorry,
不包含任何，设置为 false。
noImplicitAny, setting this to false.
所以这个选项不允许使用 ImplicitAnys，我希望允许它们。
So this option disallows ImplicitAnys and
I wish to allow them.
这是一种双重否定。
It's kind of a double negative.
所以我要保存这个然后回到我们的文件。
So I'll save that and go back to our file.
实际上我们现在做得还不错。
Now we actually are doing kinda okay here.
显然有很多暗示,
There are obviously a lot of ImplicitAnys,
但我们在这里没有遇到太多问题。
but we haven't run into
too many problems here.
让我们看看，联系人，这是一个数组的 anys。
Let's see, contacts,
it's an array of anys.
这是一条关于 anys 阵列和 nevers 阵列的线索,
This is a clue around that array
of anys versus array of nevers,
我们现在处于松散状态，所以看起来我们真的完成了。
we're in a loose mode now, so
it looks like we're actually done.
让我们再做一次测试。
Let's run our test again.
迈克 · 诺斯: 很好，他们已经跑完了。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Good, so
they've finished running.
好的，这是我们做出承诺的地方，打开一个投票请求，然后
All right, and this is where we make
a commit, open up a poll request, and
把这看作是我们进入打字稿世界的立足点。
regard this as getting our foothold
into the Typescript world.
还记得第二步吗？
Anyone who remember step two?
迈克 · 诺斯: 禁止暗示，所以我们的暗示要明确。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Forbid ImplicitAnys,
so making our anys explicit.
在这里我们还有很多工作要做。
In this we're gonna have
quite a bit of work.
麦克 · 诺斯: 现在我们可以看到打字稿正在告诉我们那里的情况
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Now we can see in our
gutter here TypeScript's telling us there
有很多地方我们需要解决问题。
are many places where we
need to address things.
所以我想从 formatDate 开始，所以我们必须找到 date 的类型。
So I'd like to start with formatDate,
so we have to find a type for date.
有人知道这可能是什么吗？
Does anyone have an idea
of what this might be?
讲者二: 日期。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Date.
迈克 · 诺斯: 约会，这是个线索，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Date,
this is a clue, right?
迈克 · 诺斯: 好吧，这很令人高兴。
ToISOString,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Okay, so that's happy.
那么 getFullName 呢？
What about getFullName?
迈克 · 诺斯: 什么？
&gt;&gt; [INAUDIBLE]
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Pardon?
讲者二: 弦乐。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: String.
迈克 · 诺斯: 我们试试吧。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Let's try it.
所以我得到了错误，属性的名字,
So I'm getting errors that
Property's firstName,
中间名和 lastName 不在字符串上。
middleName, and
lastName are not on string.
必须是一个对象，对吧，上面有属性。
Got to be an object, right,
with properties on it.
迈克 · 诺斯: 所以我想应该是名字，中间名,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So I think it's
gonna be firstName, middleName,
迈克 · 诺斯: 拯救。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Save.
好的，现在看起来很开心。
Okay, so now this looks to be happy.
所以这就是我们过滤的一个字符串数组
So this ends up being kind of an array
of strings that we've filter for
丢了什么东西。
anything missing.
这可以是所有可选的，这个过滤给我提示
This could be all optional,
this filtering gives me clue that
有些东西 falsy 试图消除。
there's something falsy there
that were trying to eliminate.
如果它开始骚扰我们，我们会回来的。
We'll come back if it
starts to serve to bug us.
好吧这个看起来有点粗糙,
All right,
now this one looks a little gnarly,
所以我会选择等到最后。
so I actually would choose to
kind of wait until the end.
我们在这里遇到的问题是如果我们看看接触
The problem we're running into
here if we look at contact
我们可以从中获取各种信息。
we're accessing all sorts
of stuff off of it.
所以我们使用了大量的结构，使用了大量的结构。
So this is using a fair amount of whatever
structure, this using a lot of it.
这是我们的日期，格式日期，我们要传入的日期,
And there's our date,
formatDate we're passing in,
但如果只是这样的话，我们应该往深处走
but we should probably be
passing in deep if that's it
应该没问题，日期定义了某个地方。
should still be fine,dates
define somewhere.
不，是从上面传来的，我们没事。
No, it's coming from up here, we're good.
好吧，让我们看看地址簿，联系人。
All right, let's look at AddressBook,
so contacts.
所以很明显，这里的数组需要输入相同的内容，对吗？
So obviously, this needs to be type
the same as the array up here, right?
所有这些方法就像是一种便利，让我们可以操作底层数组。
All this method is like a convenience that
lets us operate on the underlying array.
这里我们过滤了 c，所以 c 有 firstName 和 lastName。
Here we're filtering through and there's
c, so c has firstName and lastName.
这看起来很像我们使用的数据结构
So this looks a lot like the data
structure we were working with in
下面的函数，名称部分。
the function below, the name parts.
这就是我要说的，看起来我们在好几个地方都用到了。
This is a point where I'd say, it looks
like we're using this in several places.
我可能想为此创建一个接口。
I probably want to create an interface for
this.
所以我会继续这么做。
So I will go ahead and do that.
就是这样，我们就叫它“人” ，在顶部,
There it is, so we'll just call it Person,
and up at the top,
迈克 · 诺斯: 所以我们可以这么说
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And so we would say that
联系人可能应该是一组人。
contacts should probably
in array of Persons.
而这只需要一个人。
And this will take in a single person.
有一个属性，它是 firstName 和 lastName。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Filter has a property
on it, it's firstName and lastName.
所以，我还没有确定这是必然的，它可能是一个人。
So again, I haven't identified that this
is necessarily, it could be a Person.
我的意思是，它是在检查它们是否没有定义。
I mean,
it's checking to see if they're undefined.
到目前为止，我们还没有找到不合适的理由。
It fits for now, we haven't found
a reason for it to not fit.
我想在这里记下我可能会回来,
I'd wanna make a note here that
I should probably come back,
我可能太拘束了。
I may be over-constraining this.
如果它只是一个人的某些属性，现在我正在思考它
If it's just some properties of a Person,
and now that I'm thinking about it
很可能是，你不会想要它是一个完整的东西。
it probably is, you wouldn't want
to require that it be a full thing.
迈克 · 诺斯: 这些未定义的检查让我想要使 firstName 和
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Those undefined checks
make me want to make firstName and
姓氏可选。
lastName optional.
迈克 · 诺斯: 好的，这段代码很快乐。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Okay, so
this piece of code is happy.
事实上，我们的整个通讯录看起来都很开心。
Actually, our whole
AddressBook seems to be happy.
现在我们进入了一个棘手的领域。
Now we're in the gnarly area.
为了方便起见不用到处滚动,
And just for convenience and being
able to not scroll all over the place,
我想把这个移下去，这样就近了。
I wanna move this down so it's close by.
好的我们有个问候语,
All right, we have a salutation,
向空字符串后退的称呼。
salutation falling back
to an empty string.
这是一个线索，一个字符串可能在这里工作。
That's a clue that a string
would probably work here.
迈克 · 诺斯: 事实上，我需要一个后备计划，这说明有可能
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And the fact that I need
a fallback at all suggests it could be
Falsy.
falsy.
我猜它可能是一个空字符串，但这应该没问题。
I guess maybe it could be an empty string,
but this should be okay.
好吧那我们有电话和地址了。
Okay, then we've got phones and addresses.
有人有什么想法吗？
Anyone have an idea for this?
这是否向任何人暗示了这个值的特定形状？
Does this suggest a particular
shape of this value to anyone?
演讲者3: 操作码 迈克 · 诺斯: 这是一个物体,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Op code.
&gt;&gt; Mike North: It's an object,
反对钥匙。
Object.keys.
迈克 · 诺斯: 差不多就是这样，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So
something like that, right?
这就是 Object.keys 想要的，它想要一个对象。
That's what Object.keys wants,
it wants an object.
让我们看看，这个类型错误,
Let's see, this type error,
迈克 · 诺斯: 看起来我快到了
&gt;&gt; Mike North: It looks like I am reaching
然后传入 pHName。
into that object and passing in pHName.
这个错误消息是一个很好的遵循。
This error messages is
pretty good one to follow.
它建议我们下一步做什么？
What does it suggest we do next?
迈克 · 诺斯: 我们漏掉了什么？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: What are we missing?
说话人4: 和 phName 到您的手机属性。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: And
phName to your phones property.
Mike North: PhName 只是一个字符串。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: PhName is just a string.
讲者四: 钥匙。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Keys.
迈克 · 诺斯: 我正在看这个，它没有索引签名。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: I'm looking at
this it has no index signature.
让我们添加一个索引签名，因为我们正在获取一个任意的字符串。
Let's add an index signature,
cuz we're taking an arbitrary string.
我们只知道字符串在运行时是什么，对吗？
We only know what the string
is at runtime, right?
我们只是遍历所有的键，把这个键传入。
We're just iterating over all of the keys,
passing that key in.
这就是字典访问的样子。
This is what dictionary access looks like.
这里我们可以传入一个键，然后返回一个值。
Where we can pass in a key and
we get a value back.
这就是我们需要的。
So this is where we need.
迈克 · 诺斯: 差不多吧，我打赌地址是类似的。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Something like that, and
I'm gonna bet addresses is similar.
我们可以看一下，但是 AddrName，让我们证明给自己看。
We could look at it, but AddrName,
let's just prove it to ourselves.
在这里，到达地址对象，传入关键字,
Here it is, reach in to the addresses
object, pass in the key,
取出价值，对吗？
get the value out, right?
一个字典或者数组关联者的告密符号，按值传递键。
Telltale sign of a dictionary or an
associate of array, passing key at value.
迈克 · 诺斯: 那么现在我们需要弄清楚这些东西是什么,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So now we need to
figure out what these things are,
迈克 · 诺斯: 我们找到了地址,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So we've got on address,
房号，街道，城市，国家，州，邮政编码。
houseNumber, street, city,
country, state, postalCode.
我来做一些合理的推测
I'm gonna just make some
reasonable guesses for
这些都是基于我所认为的类型。
these based on what I
think the type should be.
编号，号码，街道，绳子,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: HouseNumber,
number, street, string,
城市，迈克诺斯: 是一根弦,
city,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Is a string,
state 是一个字符串，postalCode 看起来像一个数字
state is a string,
postalCode seems like a number
可能是根绳子，没关系。
could be a string,
it doesn't really matter.
这些都是一些字符串或者内插的东西。
These are all just sort of strings or
interpolated things.
好的，联系人有一个电子邮件属性。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Okay, and
contact has an email property.
迈克 · 诺斯: 我身边酒吧里的所有红色都消失了。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And all of my red
in my side bar has gone away here.
这样我就可以在 VS 代码中显示更多的信息,
Just so I can show you one more place
where this information pops up in VS Code,
这里有个问题标签。
there's this Problems tab.
因为我一直在打开
And cuz I've been opening and
关闭了很多文件，其中一些与我们这里的例子无关。
closing a lot of files, some of these
are not related to our example here.
但是这在你的代码中给了你一些小小的症结,
But this gives you sort of little
sticking points within your code,
编译器发现错误的位置。
places where the compiler
is finding errors.
所以我们开始了，这将是另一个提交。
So there we go, and
this would be another commit.
因为我们必须进行测试，我们不能忘记。
Because we've gotta run our test,
we can't forget that.
我不期待任何问题，因为我认为我们只是添加类型信息。
I don't expect any problems, cuz I think
we were just adding type information.
有一个问题。
There is a problem.
演讲者5: 我觉得手机的型号不对。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 5: I think phones has
the wrong type for the value.
麦克 · 诺斯: 谢谢，手机的型号与价值不符。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Thank you,
phones has the wrong type for the value.
让我们来看看这个，在 fixture 数据中看看 postalCode 应该是一个数字。
Let's look at this, look in the fixture
data postalCode should be a number.
所以我们在测试中得到了一个类型错误。
So we're getting a type error
in the tests themselves.
我们去解决这个问题，还有你们的手机，这里什么都没有。
Let's go address that, and
your phones, there's nothing here.
你是否建议它应该是一个数字？
Did you suggest it should be a number?
迈克 · 诺斯: 这里看起来什么都有可能,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: It looks
anything stringifiable here,
如果测试结果令人满意，我愿意接受数字。
I'm willing to accept number
if the tests are happy.
迈克 · 诺斯: 好吧，让我们看看还有什么要做的。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: All right,
let's see what else we got to do.
类型字符串不能分配给编号，它是一个字符串,
Type string is not assignable to number,
it's a string,
迈克 · 诺斯: 就是这样，所以
&gt;&gt; Mike North: There we go, so
现在我们知道我们的背部和正常状态，假设我们的测试覆盖率是好的。
now we know our back and our normal state,
assuming our test coverage is good.
你可以看到我们有多么依赖测试覆盖率来确保我们没有
You see how much we are leaning on
the test coverage to make sure we haven't
大幅度地改变代码，从而导致问题。
substantially alter the code in
a way that will cause problems.
这里的最后一个阶段是回到 tsconfig,
And the last phase here is going
to be going back to our tsconfig,
启用严格模式，严格: 真,
enabling strict mode, strict: true,
真实的，严格的检查: 真实的和
strictFunctionTypes: true,
strictNullChecks: true and
这不重要，因为我们没有使用 BindCallApply。
not that it matters cuz we're
not using BindCallApply.
但是为了完整性，我们也会设置这个，幸运的是,
But for completeness we'll set
up that as well, and luckily,
我在这里没有看到任何错误。
I don't see any errors here.
所以我们的第三步是一个没有任何新东西出现的停机状态。
So it turns out our third step was kind
of a no-op where nothing new popped up.
实际上，我们到达终点时，只有禁止的隐含条目。
We actually got to the finish line
with only forbidding implicit entries.
但这完全有可能
But it would be totally possible for
在松散模式下可以弹出的新东西
new things to pop-up that were fine
in the loose mode, and sort of only
一旦我们打开那些编译器的标志，就成了真正的违规。
became true violations once we
turn those compiler flags on.
什么事？
Yes?
扬声器6: 所以如果我在写界面的时候不小心加了逗号。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: So if I accidentally added
commas as I was writing my interface.
看起来这些都不错。
It seems like those are fine to do.
Mike North: 它们是，逗号是在键-值对和接口之间找到的。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: They are, commas are find
between key-value pairs and interfaces.
我喜欢使用分号的原因是，它可以帮助我在视觉上
The reason I prefer to use semicolons is,
it helps me visually
标识对象类型和对象值之间的区别。
identify the difference between and
an object type and object value.
正如你所指出的，两者都很好。
As you point out, both are fine.
我使用更漂亮的自动格式化的东西，每次我保存，和
I use prettier to automatically
format things every time I save, and
用分号代替逗号。
it's gonna replace commas with semicolons.